I am overwhelmed and overwhelmed by the
amount of information that has been
coming at me always but for the last two
weeks especially since Trump has gotten
into office it's just saying after
saying executive order after executive
order and firings and protests and
tweets and it's overwhelming and I think
our current way of staying up to den up
to date on current events isn't working
anymore it doesn't work for me it leaves
me overwhelmed and like I have this tiny
bit of information on dozens if not
hundreds of topics instead of being able
to know for certain or certain as
possible what is going on in the world
and I think both sides need it we need a
place to go that is a board we were able
to verify facts and discuss the context
around those facts without discussing
the actual opinion and implication of
those facts that can happen once we've
agreed on the facts like one facts I
need to be buried all but one who's
agreed that those are that the facts
exist there's no such thing as
alternative fact and so two of the
instances I've seen and since Trump's
inauguration that are more great area
not even but like that I can see it from
the other side or at least why the other
side has the opinions they do one is the
picture in an arguer of the
inaugurations of Obama and Trump side by
side I don't think you can dispute there
are more people in the obama one
supposedly people out but there's more
people but then the context around those
photos i think can be disputed me
discussed what time of day were the
photos taken what time of day was the
speeches were they taken I don't know
what time adidas features were what kind
of weather was out on both days and a
greater historical context I would like
to know similar photos at similar times
a day for both bush and Clinton as well
and that's not even that important to
the news story all the things that have
happened since inauguration day I feel
it more important to be able to verify
the facts be like there's these two
pictures when were they taken how Renee
taken one of the other headlines was um
entire senior management staff the US
State Department resigned and big deal
except that when dozens of my friends
reported it on Facebook there was a
comment on one of their their news feeds
that that's normal that's what happens
when a new president takes over is
certain positions resign and the
president then appoints or elec whatever
appoints people to that position
sometimes he rehires the old ones as an
MC has new one or it could have been she
but let's be clear if you okay so he
elects anyway so that's normal then
there's people who say that it's this is
unprecedented levels will those are both
verifiable I would like to know under
Trump under Obama again also under Bush
and Clinton how many people resign in
each department both total numbers and
percentages and is that normal is it
unprecedented is unprecedented that
there's two percent more it's like 90
versus ninety-two percent of people or
is it like five percent you should
resign and now it's like ninety-five
percent those are very different and
it's not just click bait it's verifiable
fact I want to know what is going on I
want to know who what air strikes are
happening where and by whom to whom I
want to know what protests are happening
who was being protested what's happening
law enforcement wise against or for
those protests I want to know what's
going on in a more verifiable way where
it's not just opinion and what's being
discussed about facts that were somehow
able to twist and alters to say what we
want them to say and we're all
susceptible to it or susceptible to the
head
is that grab our attention and make us
want to click on them and I want to be
able to click on it and then also be
able to verify that what we're talking
about how accurate is it has it been
disproven has it been is there something
currently that has is more relevant to
this exact topic and I think we can do
that with one website that we all own
and we can contribute to where we talk
about the facts we can have discussions
about what those facts mean but that
there's one place for the facts you can
go to selling posts to pictures side by
side of two different observations eight
years apart someone else can post that
same picture on the site and we can talk
about when it was taken and the
difference in timeline and what that
means and so we can't have the media
spin we can't have the new president
spin we have actual verifiable fact in a
way that we can easily see what is going
on right now and what needs to be done
no matter which side you're on if you're
riding against can mature supporting him
if you're whatever it happens to be I
want a space where facts are verifiable
because there is no such thing as
alternative facts